Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - 9-55-162 to 9-55-263, 1955-09 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-10 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - October 1955 magazine (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - 10-55-000 to 10-55-125, 1955-10 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - 10-55-127 to 10-55-212, 1955-10 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 10-55-213 to 10-55-308, 1955-10 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - 10-55-309 to 10-55-399, 1955-10 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-11 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - November 1955 magazine (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 11-55-000 to 11-55-089, 1955-11 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - 11-55-090 to 11-55-188, 1955-11 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 11-55-190 to 11-55-333, 1955-11 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-12 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - December 1955 magazine (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 12-55-001 to 12-55-110, 1955-12 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 12-55-111 to 12-55-181, 1955-12 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 12-55-182 to 12-55-255, 1955-12 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-01 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - January 1956 magazine (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 1-56-000 to 1-56-147, 1956-01 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-02 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - February 1956 magazine (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 2-56-000 to 2-56-092, 1956-02 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 2-56-093 to 2-56-167, 1956-02 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 2-56-168 to 2-56-249, 1956-02 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-03 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - March 1956 magazine (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 3-56-000 to 3-56-076, 1956-03 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 3-56-077 to 3-56-155, 1956-03 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 3-56-157 to 3-56-221, 1956-03 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 3-56-223 to 3-56-331, 1956-03 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - April 1956 magazine (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 4-56-000 to 4-56-089, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - 4-56-090 to 4-56-183, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - 4-56-185 to 4-56-265, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - 4-56-266 to 4-56-322, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - 4-56-324 to 4-56-395, 1956-04 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-05 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - May 1956 magazine (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - 5-56-001 to 5-56-083, 1956-05 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 5-56-086 to 5-56-227, 1956-05 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 5-56-216 to 5-56-271, 1956-05 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 5-56-272 to 5-56-382, 1956-05 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-06 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - June 1956 magazine (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 6-56-000 to 6-56-072, 1956-06 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - 6-56-077 to 6-56-149, 1956-06 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - 6-56-152 to 6-56-246, 1956-06 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - 6-56-249 to 6-56-348, 1956-06 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-07 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - July 1956 magazine (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - 7-56-000 to 7-56-064, 1956-07 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 7-56-067 to 7-56-137, 1956-07 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 7-56-138 to 7-56-254, 1956-07 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-08 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - August 1956 magazine (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 8-56-000 to 8-56-066, 1956-08 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - 8-56-067 to 8-56-144, 1956-08 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 8-56-149 to 8-56-220, 1956-08 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-09 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - September 1956 magazine (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 9-56-000 to 9-56-059, 1956-09 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 9-56-060 to 9-56-157, 1956-09 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 9-56-158 to 9-56-226, 1956-09 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - 9-56-221 to 9-56-300, 1956-09 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-10 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - October 1956 magazine (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - 10-56-000 to 10-56-072, 1956-10 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 10-56-078 to 10-56-191, 1956-10 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 10-56-192 to 10-56-313, 1956-10 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-11 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - November 1956 magazine (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - 11-56-000 to 11-56-078, 1956-11 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 11-56-079 to 11-56-161, 1956-11 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 11-56-166 to 11-56-253, 1956-11 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1956-12 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - December 1956 magazine (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 12-56-000 to 12-56-078, 1956-12 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 12-56-079 to 12-56-182, 1956-12 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - 12-56-183 to 12-56-249, 1956-12 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 12-56-250 to 12-56-308, 1956-12 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-01 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - January 1957 magazine (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 1-57-000 to 1-57-139, 1957-01 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-02 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - February 1957 magazine (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - 2-57-000 to 2-57-090, 1957-02 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - 2-57-092 to 2-57-165, 1957-02 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - 2-57-166 to 2-57-258, 1957-02 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-03 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - March 1957 magazine (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 3-57-000 to 3-57-058, 1957-03 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 3-57-059 to 3-57-189, 1957-03 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 3-57-191 to 3-57-257, 1957-03 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 3-57-258 to 3-57-349, 1957-03 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-04 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - April 1957 magazine (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 4-57-001 to 4-57-067, 1957-04 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 4-57-068 to 4-57-164, 1957-04 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 4-57-165 to 4-57-253, 1957-04 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 4-57-254 to 4-57-365, 1957-04 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-05 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - May 1957 magazine (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 5-57-000 to 5-57-089, 1957-05 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 5-57-090 to 5-57-178, 1957-05 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 5-57-179 to 5-57-261, 1957-05 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 5-57-262 to 5-57-376, 1957-05 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-06 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - June 1957 magazine (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 6-57-000 to 6-57-095, 1957-06 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 6-57-096 to 6-57-196, 1957-06 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 6-57-199 to 6-57-307, 1957-06 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-07 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - July 1957 magazine (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 7-57-001 to 7-57-075, 1957-07 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 7-57-076 to 7-57-181, 1957-07 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-08 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - August 1957 magazine (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - 8-57-000 to 8-57-072, 1957-08 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 8-57-073 to 8-57-129, 1957-08 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - 8-57-132 to 8-57-208, 1957-08 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-09 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - September 1957 magazine (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - 9-57-001 to 9-57-078, 1957-09 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 9-57-080 to 9-57-131, 1957-09 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 9-57-132 to 9-57-186, 1957-09 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 9-57-187 to 9-57-266, 1957-09 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-10 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - October 1957 magazine (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - 10-57-001 to 10-57-156, 1957-10 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - 10-57-160 to 10-57-251, 1957-10 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - 10-57-252 to 10-57-325, 1957-10 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-11 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - November 1957 magazine (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - 11-57-009 to 11-57-081, 1957-11 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - 11-57-082 to 11-57-182, 1957-11 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - 11-57-163 to 11-57-226, 1957-11 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - 11-57-228 to 11-57-305, 1957-11 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1957-12 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - December 1957 magazine (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - 12-57-000 to 12-57-044, 1957-12 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - 12-57-047 to 12-57-093, 1957-12 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - 12-57-094 to 12-57-168, 1957-12 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - 12-57-169 to 12-57-242, 1957-12 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-01 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - January 1958 magazine (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - 1-58-001 to 1-58-071, 1958-01 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - 1-58-072 to 1-58-166, 1958-01 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-02 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - February 1958 magazine (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - 2-58-000 to 2-58-062, 1958-02 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - 2-58-065 to 2-58-140, 1958-02 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - 2-58-141 to 2-58-206, 1958-02 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-03 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - March 1958 magazine, 1958-03 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - 3-58-001 to 3-58-075, 1958-03 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - 3-58-076 to 3-58-156, 1958-03 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - 3-58-157 to 3-58-271, 1958-03 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-04 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - April 1958 magazine (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - 4-58-000 to 4-58-083, 1958-04 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 4-58-084 to 4-58-135, 1958-04 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 4-58-136 to 4-58-248, 1958-04 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - 4-58-249 to 4-58-366, 1958-04 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, North, 1958-05 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - May 1958 magazine (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - 5-58-000 to 5-58-105, 1958-05 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 5-58-116 to 5-58-205, 1958-05 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - 5-58-206 to 5-58-263, 1958-05 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - 5-58-264 to 5-58-341, 1958-05 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-06 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - June 1958 magazine (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - 6-58-000 to 6-58-092, 1958-06 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - 6-58-093 to 6-58-145, 1958-06 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - 6-58-146 to 6-58-246, 1958-06 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-07 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - July 1958 magazine (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - 7-58-000 to 7-58-044, 1958-07 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - 7-58-045 to 7-58-166, 1958-07 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - 7-58-167 to 7-58-266, 1958-07 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-08 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - August 1958 magazine (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - 8-58-000 to 8-58-082, 1958-08 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - 8-58-083 to 8-58-107, 1958-08 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - 8-58-108 to 8-58-216, 1958-08 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-09 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - September 1958 magazine (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - 9-58-000 to 9-58-088, 1958-09 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - 9-58-098 to 9-58-147, 1958-09 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - 9-58-148 to 9-58-246, 1958-09 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-10 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - October 1958 magazine (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - 10-58-000 to 10-58-074, 1958-10 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - 10-58-075 to 10-58-180, 1958-10 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - 10-58-181 to 10-58-251, 1958-10 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - 10-58-252 to 10-58-338, 1958-10 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-11 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - November 1958 magazine (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - 11-58-000 to 11-58-081, 1958-11 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 11-58-082 to 11-58-153, 1958-11 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - 11-58-155 to 11-58-229, 1958-11 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 11-58-230 to 11-58-300, 1958-11 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1958-12 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - December 1958 magazine (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - 12-58-000 to 12-58-060, 1958-12 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - 12-58-061 to 12-58-106, 1958-12 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - 12-58-107 to 12-58-193, 1958-12 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-01 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - January 1959 magazine (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - 1-59-000 to 1-59-095, 1959-01 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - 1-59-097 to 1-59-164, 1959-01 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-02 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - February 1959 magazine (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - 2-59-000 to 2-59-103, 1959-02 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 2-59-104 to 2-59-180, 1959-02 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-03 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - March 1959 magazine (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - 3-59-000 to 3-59-085, 1959-03 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - 3-59-088 to 3-59-174, 1959-03 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - 3-59-175 to 3-59-269, 1959-03 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-04 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - April 1959 magazine (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - 4-59-000 to 4-59-098, 1959-04 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - 4-59-100 to 4-59-178, 1959-04 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - 4-59-179 to 4-59-246, 1959-04 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - 4-59-247 to 4-59-326, 1959-04 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - 4-59-328 to 4-59-372, 1959-04 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-05 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - May 1959 magazine (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - 5-59-001 to 5-59-058, 1959-05 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - 5-59-059 to 5-59-117, 1959-05 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - 5-59-119 to 5-59-233, 1959-05 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - 5-59-234 to 5-59-327, 1959-05 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-06 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - June 1959 magazine, 1959-06 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - 6-59-001 to 6-59-097, 1959-06 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - 6-59-098 to 6-59-198, 1959-06 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - 6-59-200 to 6-59-268, 1959-06 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-07 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - July 1959 magazine (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - 7-59-000 to 7-59-088, 1959-07 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 7-59-089 to 7-59-176, 1959-07 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - 7-59-177 to 7-59-260, 1959-07 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-08 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - August 1959 magazine (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - 8-59-001 to 8-59-089, 1959-08 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - 8-59-090 to 8-59-252, 1959-08 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-09 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - September 1959 magazine (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - 9-59-000 to 9-59-060, 1959-09 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - 9-59-061 to 9-59-160, 1959-09 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - 9-59-167 to 9-59-269, 1959-09 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-10 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - October 1959 magazine (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - 10-59-001 to 10-59-148, 1959-10 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - 10-59-147 to 10-59-248, 1959-10 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 10-59-249 to 10-59-301, 1959-10 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - 10-59-303 to 10-59-406, 1959-10 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-11 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - November 1959 magazine (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - 11-59-000 to 11-59-089, 1959-11 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - 11-50-090 to 11-59-177, 1959-11 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - 11-59-178 to 11-59-243, 1959-11 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - 11-59-244 to 11-59-323, 1959-11 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1959-12 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - December 1959 magazine (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - 12-59-000 to 12-59-080, 1959-12 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - 12-59-081 to 12-59-137, 1959-12 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - 12-59-138 to 12-59-215, 1959-12 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-01 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - January 1960 magazine (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - 1-60-072 to 1-60-196, 1960-01 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 1-60-072 to 1-60-196, 1960-01 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-02 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - February 1960 magazine (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - 2-60-001 to 2-60-091, 1960-02 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - 2-60-103 to 2-60-192, 1960-02 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - 2-60-193 to 2-60-278, 1960-02 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-03 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - March 1960 magazine (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - 3-60-000 to 3-60-090, 1960-03 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - 3-60-091 to 3-60-184, 1960-03 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - 3-60-185 to 3-60-226, 1960-03 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - 3-60-230 to 3-60-277, 1960-03 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - 3-60-278 to 3-60-398, 1960-03 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-04 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - April 1960 magazine (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - 4-60-002 to 4-60-073, 1960-04 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - 4-60-080 to 4-60-189, 1960-04 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - 4-60-190 to 4-60-261, 1960-04 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - 4-60-262 to 4-60-335, 1960-04 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - 4-60-336 to 4-60-428, 1960-04 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-05 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - May 1960 magazine (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - 5-60-001 to 5-60-077, 1960-05 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - 5-60-079 to 5-60-159, 1960-05 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - 5-60-160 to 5-60-239, 1960-05 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - 5-60-240 to 5-60-300, 1960-05 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - 5-60-301 to 5-60-339, 1960-05 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 5-60-340 to 5-60-416, 1960-05 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-06 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - June 1960 magazine (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - 6-60-002 to 6-60-078, 1960-06 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - 6-60-079 to 6-60-157, 1960-06 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - 6-60-158 to 6-60-211, 1960-06 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - 6-60-212 to 6-60-284, 1960-06 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - 6-60-285 to 6-60-361, 1960-06 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-07 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - July 1960 magazine (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - 7-60-002 to 7-60-065, 1960-07 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - 7-60-066 to 7-60-131, 1960-07 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - 7-60-137 to 7-60-215, 1960-07 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-08 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - August 1960 magazine (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - 8-60-002 to 8-60-053, 1960-08 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - 8-60-054 to 8-60-138, 1960-08 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - 8-60-139 to 8-60-224, 1960-08 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-09 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - September 1960 Central magazine, 1960-09 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - 9-60-001 to 9-60-070, 1960-09 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - 9-60-071 to 9-60-146, 1960-09 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - 9-60-147 to 9-60-232, 1960-09 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-10 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - October 1960 magazine (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - 10-60-002 to 10-60-071, 1960-10 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - 10-60-072 to 10-60-147, 1960-10 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - 10-60-148 to 10-60-238, 1960-10 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - 10-60-239 to 10-60-306, 1960-10 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-11 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - November 1960 magazine (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - 11-60-001 to 11-60-074, 1960-11 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - 11-60-076 to 11-60-146, 1960-11 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - 11-60-147 to 11-60-207, 1960-11 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - 11-060-210 to 11-60-2999, 1960-11 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - 11-60-300 to 11-60-366, 1960-11 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1960-12 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - December 1960 magazine (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - 12-60-002 to 12-60-064, 1960-12 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - 12-60-065 to 12-60-122, 1960-12 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - 12-60-123 to 12-60-180, 1960-12 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-03 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-01 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - 2-61-110 to 2-61-181, 1961-02 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - 2-61-057 to 2-61-105, 1961-02 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - 2-61-002 to 2-61-057, 1961-02 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - February 1961 magazine (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, South and North, 1961-02 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - 1-61-080 to 1-61-147, 1961-01 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - 1-61-002 to 1-61-079, 1961-01 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - January 1961 magazine (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - March 1961 magazine (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - 3-61-001 to 3-61-072, 1961-03 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - 3-61-072 to 3-61-151, 1961-03 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - 3-61-152 to 3-61-247, 1961-03 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - 3-61-248 to 3-61-319, 1961-03 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-04 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - April 1961 magazine (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - 4-61-002 to 4-61-064, 1961-04 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - 4-61-065 to 4-61-153, 1961-04 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - 4-61-154 to 4-61-266, 1961-04 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - 4-61-267 to 4-61-375, 1961-04 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-05 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - May 1961 magazine (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - 5-61-000 to 5-61-084, 1961-05 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - 5-61-086 to 5-61-150, 1961-05 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - 5-61-151 to 5-61-213, 1961-05 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - 5-61-214 to 5-61-318, 1961-05 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - 5-61-320 to 5-61-387, 1961-05 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - June 1961 magazine (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - 6-61-003 to 6-61-077, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - 6-61-078 to 6-61-153, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - 6-61-154 to 6-61-215, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - 6-61-216 to 6-61-275, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - 6-61-276 to 6-61-366, 1961-06 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-07 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - July 1961 magazine (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - 7-61-001 to 7-61-108, 1961-07 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - 7-61-109 to 7-61-209, 1961-07 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-08 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - August 1961 magazine (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - 8-61-002 to 8-61-066, 1961-08 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - 8-61-067 to 8-61-150, 1961-08 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - 8-61-151 to 8-61-212, 1961-08 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-09 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - September 1961 magazine (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - 9-61-001 to 9-61-067, 1961-09 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - 9-61-068 to 9-61-133, 1961-09 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - 9-61-134 to 9-61-197, 1961-09 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - 9-61-198 to 9-61-257, 1961-09 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - 9-61-268 to 9-61-309, 1961-09 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-10 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - October 1961 magazine (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - 10-61-002 to 10-61-072, 1961-10 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - 10-61-074 to 10-61-144, 1961-10 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - 10-61-151 to 10-61-238, 1961-10 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - 10-61-238 to 10-61-285, 1961-10 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - 10-61-286 to 10-61-354, 1961-10 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1961-10 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - November 1961 magazine (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - 11-61-002 to 11-61-099, 1961-11 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - 11-61-100 to 11-61-172, 1961-11 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - 11-61-173 to 11-61-258, 1961-11 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, North and South, 1961-12 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - December 1961 magazine (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - 12-61-002 to 12-61-079, 1961-12 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - 12-61-081 to 12-61-166, 1961-12 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, North and South, 1962-01 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - January 1962 magazine (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - 1-62-002 to 1-62-062, 1962-01 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - 1-62-063 to 1-62-132, 1962-01 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - 1-62-134 to 1-62-192, 1962-01 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-02 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - February 1962 magazine (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - 2-62-001 to 2-62-078, 1962-02 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - 2-62-091 to 2-62-190, 1962-02 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-03 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - March 1962 magazine (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - 3-62-000 to 3-62-067, 1962-03 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - 3-62-068 to 3-62-154, 1962-03 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - 3-62-155 to 3-62-251, 1962-03 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - 3-62-253 to 3-62-372, 1962-03 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-04 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - April 1962 magazine (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - 4-62-001 to 4-62-085, 1962-04 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - 4-62-086 to 4-62-149, 1962-04 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - 4-62-150 to 4-62-241, 1962-04 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - 4-62-242 to 4-62-320, 1962-04 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-05 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - May 1962 magazine (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - 5-62-001 to 5-62-069, 1962-05 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - 5-62-070 to 5-62-150, 1962-05 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - 5-62-151 to 5-62-214, 1962-05 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - 5-62-215 to 5-62-302, 1962-05 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-06 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - June 1962 magazine (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - 6-62-001 to 6-62-086, 1962-06 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - 6-62-087 to 6-62-220, 1962-06 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-07 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - July 1962 magazine (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - 7-62-000 to 7-62-065, 1962-07 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - 7-62-068 to 7-62-142, 1962-07 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - 7-62-143 to 7-62-291, 1962-07 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-08 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - August 1962 magazine (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - 8-62-001 to 8-62-291, 1962-08 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - 8-62-292 to 8-62-386, 1962-08 (Box 124, Folder 6)